{
    "id": "00412f07a4f8470ca2db503a647cbabe",
    "title": "Though And Although",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "....................................... my grandmother is very old, she can still read without glasses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ed1ec8179db4224876feeebdd7a9fb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... he was very tired, he completed the work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Although",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d703120a44e4f91b309009049ddcde0"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... the policemen ran fast, they couldn’t catch the thief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Even if",
                "As though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec79b0f0bcc54285b46b481c0f12fbea"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. they gave him the best medical care, they could not save his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "944f261096d14b8b93fe3148b1d65b10"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... he left home early, he arrived late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2a3cddd9786b4cc2876b2316396cb462"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ she had the required qualifications, she did not get the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As though",
                "Even if",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b578f8dc57742f4a33931a64a490233"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... they are rich, they lead simple lives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Although",
                "As though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02596645e6704f12962a25b549f3a1bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ she was ill, she went to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94c6cf3808a946338a7b20cfaa232896"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. our team played well, they could not win the championship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af1f1f9e933d4935b9c84128ee5f93a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... my grandmother can’t read or write, she is wiser than most people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Even if",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c223540ff764c7e913a9e748a4b4359"
        }
    ]
}